&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我把这个带到一个我想做的案例中，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let me bring this down to a case that I wanna make,
这更像是一个直接的案件，而不是
and this is much more of a direct case than
我以前从来没有谈过这个话题。
I've never made before about this topic.
在此之前的大部分时间，我的基本外带或
Most of the time prior to this point, my essential takeaway or
我向人们传达的基本信息是，=和=可以在您的代码中共存，
my essential message to people was, == and === can coexist in your code,
你可以做出选择，你不必回避=，
and you can make choices, you don't have to avoid the ==,
我将对这一点进行更有力的论证。
I'm going to make a stronger argument to this point.
更强的论点是，您应该在所有可能的地方都倾向于=。
The stronger argument that you should prefer == in all possible places.
我知道这会让一些人震惊，但是
And I know this gonna shock a few people but
你必须要有一个开放的心态去听这个论点。
you're gonna have to have an open mind to listen to this argument.
把我们一起讨论过的所有事情统统放在一起，
Taking everything in whole in totality that we've talked about together,
包括这一事实，即我声称理解类型的代码是
including the fact that it is my claim that code that understands types is
无论选择什么，代码都会更好。
better code regardless of the choice.
在这种情况下，我认为我可以证明=比=更可取。
Within that context, I think I can make the case that == is preferable to ===.
&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：所以知道类型总是比不知道类型好。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So knowing the types is always better than not knowing them.
代码的不确定性是使代码难以阅读的原因，
The uncertainty of code is what make code hard to read,
它使代码容易受到错误的影响。
it makes code susceptible to bugs.
对于不知道自己类型的问题，有些人会说，我需要
Some people respond to that problem of not knowing their types by saying, I need to
将我的编码风格更改为使用静态键入，如typescript和其他。
change my coding style to use static typing, like TypeScript and the others.
我们稍后会讨论打字脚本，但是
We're gonna talk about TypeScript in just a moment but
我认为这不是解决这个问题的唯一办法。
I don't think that that is the only response to this problem.
对这个问题还有另一种反应，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以
There's another response to this problem, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
=不是关于与未知类型的比较，这不是它的目的
== is not about comparisons with unknown type, that's not what it's for and that's
不是你应该用它来做什么，这与大多数人声称的相反。
not what you should use it for, that is the opposite of what most people claim.
大多数人声称他们在不知道类型时使用=，然后他们
Most people claim that they use == when they don't know the types, and then they
落入这些bug中，我是说，在那种情况下，根本不要使用它。
fall into these bugs and I'm saying don't use it in that scenario at all.
当你不知道类型时，永远不要使用=。
Never use the == when you don't know the types, ever.
只有在知道类型时才使用=。
Only use the == when you know the types.
正如我所说的，您应该努力了解您的
And as I said, you should strive to know the types in your
尽可能多的比较。
comparisons as much as possible.
它是关于与已知类型的比较，也是可选的，
It's about comparisons with known types and optionally,
如果你喜欢强迫的话。
if you like to have coercions.
也许你所有的比较你都知道类型和
Maybe all of your comparisons you know the types and
也许所有这些类型都是平等的，你从不使用强制，而且
maybe all of those types are always equal and you never use coercion, and
在这种情况下，=还是更可取的。
still in that scenario == is preferable.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：但也许有些时候你想利用
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: But maybe some of the times you wanna take advantage
强迫，然后=基本上是你唯一的选择。
of coercion, and then == is essentially your only option.
&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：所以让我们深入了解这里的细微差别，因为我认识你们中的一些人
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's dig into the nuance here because I know some of you
不会一下子就相信我的，好吗？
are not gonna believe me just right off the bat, okay?
让我们深入了解这里的细微差别，如果你知道比较中的类型，
Let's dig into the nuance here, if you know the types in a comparison,
我觉得你应该。
and I think you should.
如果您知道比较中的类型，并且这两种类型相同，
If you know the types in a comparison and both of the types are the same,
那么我们已经知道=等同于=。
then we already know that == is identical to ===.
我们已经知道它们的可互换性，在您了解它们的情况下
We already know their interchangeable, in the case where you know them and
它们是一样的。
they are the same.
所以你是说，是的，但这并不意味着我不知道如何使用它。
So you're saying, yeah, but that doesn't mean that I don't know how to use it.
我的主张是，在这种情况下使用=是不必要的，而且
My claim is, using === is unnecessary in that scenario and
你应该更喜欢较短的=。
you should prefer the shorter ==.
这不仅仅是少用一个角色，好吗？
That is not just about using one fewer character, okay?
你们中的一些人知道打字稿做了很多工作，
Some of you know that TypeScript does a lot of work,
即使你根本不做任何类型的工作。
even if you don’t do any types at all.
在这里，我没有任何类型被注释过一次，所以一直都没有
Here I have no types annotated once so ever and
它仍然会做一系列的推断，类型推断，好吗？
it still does a bunch of inference, type inference, okay?
在这种特殊的情况下，错误告诉我不应该使用a=
In this particular case what the error is telling me is I should not use a ===
因为类型是不同的，这将永远是假的。
because the types are different, and this will always be false.
现在我不知道你怎么想，但是
Now I don't know about you, but
我发现这是一个特别有用的错误消息。
I find that to be a particularly useful error message.
它告诉我不要做那些永远都会失败的蠢事，
It is telling me don't do something stupid that would always fail,
100%，保证会失败，好吗？
100%, guaranteed to fail, all right?
它知道它会失败，它告诉我不要做不必要的事情。
It knows that it'll fail, and it tells me don't do it unnecessarily.
我的主张是，如果我们发现合理，
My claim is that if we find to be reasonable,
那么反阳性也是合理的。
then the counter positive is also reasonable.
如果在类型不匹配时使用它是没有意义的，
If it is pointless to use it when the types don't match,
当类型匹配时，没有必要使用它。
it is unnecessary to use it when the types do match.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果我们喜欢让我们的Linter在毫无意义的时候抱怨，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If we like for our linter to complain when it'd be pointless,
那么我们应该有一个在不必要的时候抱怨的Linter。
then we ought to have a linter that complains when it's unnecessary.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以如果你知道比较中的类型，并且它们是不同的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So if you know the types in a comparison, and they're different,
这就是事情变得有趣的地方
this is where things get interesting,
因为据说使用=就是保护你，拯救你。
because supposedly using the === is protecting you and saving you.
但是，如果您知道类型，并且知道它们是不同的，则单个=将
But if you know the types and you know them to be different, a single === will
总是失败，这就是我们刚刚谈到的打字规则的全部原因。
always fail, which is the whole reason for that TypeScript rule we just talked about.
&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：它肯定会被打破，你和我在一起吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It would definitely be broken, you're with me?
所以在这种情况下你唯一的两个选择，如果你知道类型和
So your only two options in that case, if you know the types and
他们和你不匹配，有两种选择，
they don't match you, have one of two options,
您可以不进行比较，也可以使用=。
you can either not do the comparison or you can use ==.
这是你唯一的两个选择
Those are your only two options and
如果你知道比较中的类型，并且它们是不同的，
if you know the types in a comparison, and they're different,
唯一等同于单个=的将是两个或更多的=。
the only equivalent to a single == would be two or more ===.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：你不能有a=和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You can not have a === and
a=当类型不同时是等价的，这是不可能的。
a == be equivalent when the types are different, that is impossible.
因此，如果您有一个场景，您可以使用一个=，或者您可以使用两个或
So if you have a scenario where you could use one ==, or you could use two or
更多=，猜猜哪个会比较慢，两个=。
more ===, guess which one is going to be slower, the two ===.
让JavaScript执行强制比使用JavaScript更快
It is faster to let JavaScript do the coercion than it is for
你要做一堆明确的。
you to make a bunch of explicit ones.
如果你必须做三次或三次，情况就会更糟
And it gets even worse if you have to do three or
四取决于强制的复杂性。
four depending upon the complexity of the coercion.
现在我说慢一点，用空气引号，因为我们谈论的是微秒。
Now I say slower, in air quotes because we're talking about microseconds.
但在这种情况下，a=绝对不可能更快。
But it is absolutely not possible for a === to be faster in this scenario.
在最好的情况下，它是相等的，实际上，在现实中，
In the best possible scenario, it's equal and actually, in reality,
多次列出它们只会稍微慢一点。
it's just a tiny bit slower to list them out multiple times.
现在我并不是说仅仅从表现上来说这就是一个论点，
Now I'm not making the case that on performance alone that's an argument,
因为微秒的差异并不是那么重要。
because the microsecond difference is not that relevant.
但是，这是更大的情况的一部分，=并不在某种程度上优于=。
But this is part of the larger case that === is not somehow superior to ==.
很多人说=更快，因为它不会强迫。
Many people have said === is faster cuz it doesn't coerce.
这是苹果和橙子的比较，
That's a apples to oranges comparison,
因为你说一个=比一个=快，它们不相等。
cuz you're saying one === is faster than one == and they're not equivalent.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果你真的看着一个苹果对一个苹果，两个=总是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If you actually looked at an apples to apples two === is always
会比1=稍微慢一点。
going to be a little bit slower than one ==.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以如果你在这种情况下，你可以做两个=或
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So if you're in this scenario where you could do two === or
三四个，或者你可以做一个=，
three or four, or you could do one ==,
我说你应该更喜欢这两个中较快的一个，那就是单一=，
I say you should prefer the faster of the two which is the single ==,
论点的一部分，当然不是整个论点。
part of the argument, certainly not the entirety of the argument.
最后，如果类型不同，并且两个或更多是比较，
And finally, if the types are different, and two or more are what the comparisons,
这就是你要使用的，是两个或两个以上的=，
that's what you would use, is two or more of the ===,
我的主张是它用不必要的类型信息分散了读者的注意力，
my claim is that it's distracting the reader with unnecessary type information,
例如在未定义空值的情况下。
like in the null undefined case, for example.
没有人找到案例，你分散了读者的注意力，就是这两个
And the no one find case, you're distracting the reader there is these two
不同的空值，它们有一些奇怪的差异。
different empty values and they sort of have weird quirky differences.
在大多数情况下，读者并不需要看到这一点，
That's not necessary for the reader to see in most cases,
在大多数情况下，你通过明确列出你拥有的东西来分散他们的注意力
in most cases you're distracting them by listing explicitly and what you have
使用的是更合适的抽象强制，使用=更干净。
to use is the more properly abstracted coercion that it's cleaner with the ==.
记住，这是如果你知道类型的话，对吧，
Now remember, this is if you know the types, right,
我只是在你知道类型的情况下才会提出这些声明。
I'm only making these claims if you know the types.
通过了解类型，
And by know the types,
我的意思是，对于代码的读者来说，类型是什么是显而易见的。
I mean that it is obvious to the reader of the code what the types will be.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么，对不起，还有一个，摘要幻灯片，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So what about, sorry, there's one more, the summary slide,
当然可以。
of course.
这是如果你知道类型，所以概括地说，无论类型是否匹配，
This is if you know the types, so in summary, whether the types match or not,
=当你知道类型时是更明智的选择，好吗？
== is the more sensible choice when you know the types, okay?
当您知道类型时，=是更明智的选择，所以
When you know the types, == is the more sensible choice, so
让我们看看另一边，在那些你不知道类型的情况下。
let's look at the other side, in those cases where you don't know the types.
如果您不知道类型，这意味着您不能完全理解代码，
If you do not know the types, that means you don't fully understand the code,
这可能是一个不必要的要求。
that may be an unnecessary requirement.
不可能保证100%，你总是知道
It is not possible to guarantee 100%, you always know
整个系统中的类型，这是不合理和合理的。
the types in the entire system, that's not reasonable and rational.
所以我认识到有时候会发生比较，而且
So I recognize that there will be times when comparisons happen, and
有一些不确定性。
there's some uncertainty.
我的主张是，这应该是一种稀有，而不是现状。
My claim is that that should be a rarity rather than the status quo.
但它确实意味着，无论是稀有还是现状，就是
But what it does mean, whether it's a rarity or the status quo, is that that
由于这种不确定性，部分代码更难理解。
part of the code is harder to understand as a result of that uncertainty.
所以不知道类型意味着你不能完全理解代码。
So not knowing the types means that you don't fully understand that code.
最好的反应是折射它，这样你就可以知道类型，如果可能的话。
The best response is to refractor it so that you can know the types, if possible.
如果你不知道类型，并且
If you don't know the types, and
需要解决的就是了解的不确定性，
that uncertainty of knowing just has to be dealt,
那么至少要确保这一点对读者来说是显而易见的。
then at least make sure that that is obvious to the reader.
确保读者清楚地看到这里存在一些不确定性。
Make sure that it is obvious to the reader that there is some uncertainty here.
输入代码注释，
Put a code comment,
以一种不会让读者产生虚假安全感的方式来构建它，
structure it in such a way that the reader doesn't have a false sense of security,
他们认为他们知道发生了什么，实际上这是不确定的。
they think they know what's happening, and actually it's uncertain.
这应该是非常明显的，它在任何可能的方式下都是不确定的
It should be super obvious that it's uncertain in whatever possible way you
可以，因为我们又一次试图传达我们的意图。
can, because again we're trying to communicate our intent.
我在这里的目的是告诉你，这是不确定的，就像你知道的，
My intent here is to tell you that it's uncertain, just so you know,
小心会有龙，对吧，这就是我们想要用我们的代码做的事情。
beware there'll be dragons, right, that's what we wanna do with our code.
所以它应该对读者来说是显而易见的，并且
So it should be obvious to the reader, and
关于这种不确定性，你可以使用的最明显的信号是=。
the most obvious signal you can use about that uncertainty is ===.
如果你遵循我在第一组条款中的论点，
If you followed what I argued in the first set of clauses,
也就是说，当您知道类型时，=更可取，然后使用
which is that the == is preferable when you know the types, then the usage of
=应该为您不知道类型的情况保留。
=== should be reserved for the cases where you don't know the types.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以它向读者发出信号，我不知道类型，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So that it signals to the reader, I don't know the types,
我只是想保护自己。
I'm trying to protect myself.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它应该跳出来，读者应该看到，这里有a=。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It should jump out, the reader should see, there's a === here.
这意味着有一些类型的不确定性，并且
That means there are some uncertainty of the types, and
我们需要限制自己，这样我们就不会陷入困境。
we need to restrict ourselves so we don't run into a corner case.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：同样，我会说不知道类型是等效的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Also, I would say that not knowing the types is equivalent
到假设将发生类型转换或类型强制。
to assuming that type conversion or type coercion will occur.
这相当于假设，因为如果你不知道类型，
It's equivalent to assuming that because if you don't know the types,
最坏的情况是它们不匹配，并且在某些情况下不匹配
the worst case scenario is that they will not match and they will not match in some
奇怪的方式唤起了一些奇怪的角落里的胁迫。
weird way that invokes some weird corner case of coercion.
你需要做最坏的打算。
You need to assume the worst case.
所以不知道什么类型的等同于最坏情况下的胁迫。
So not knowing the types of equivalent to that worst case coercion.
对此唯一明智的回应是，
And the only sensible response to that,
对此唯一安全的反应是用a=保护自己。
the only safe response to that is protect yourself from that with a ===.
总而言之，如果你不能或不愿意，使用一种你可以知道和
In summary if you can't or won't, use a style where you can know and
有明显的类型，唯一合理的和
have obvious types, the only thing that is sensible and
合理的是你使用=。
reasonable is for you to use the ===.
如果使用=，这并不意味着对您的攻击。
This isn't meant to be an attack against you if use ===.
我只是试图以一种真正移动的方式重新构建这个讨论
I'm just trying to reframe this discussion in a way that actually moves
讨论向前推进，而不是一种宗教辩论，
the discussion forward rather than a sort of religious debate of well,
这本书说永远不要用它，我甚至从来没有考虑过其他任何东西。
this one book said never use it, and I've never even considered anything else.
我实际上是在试着做一套合理的分析来得出一些真实的结论
I'm actually trying to make a rational set of analysis here to come to some real
结论，不只是一个人说的话，好吗？
conclusion, not just the thing that one guy said, okay?
你可以测试我的分析，如果你不同意我的理论，没关系。
And you can test my analysis, if you don't agree with my rationale, that's okay.
但我在陈述这个案子，这样你就可以测试理由了。
But I'm laying out this case so that you can test the rationale.
我要说的是，即使在那种情况下，
And I would say this, even in that scenario,
在那里你使用=的每个地方都是一样的，
where every place that you would use a === would be the same,
它等同于a=，所以你说，你知道，我们只是想要更简单的
it would be equivalent to a ==, and so you say, you know, we just want the simpler
我们想用=到处使用的东西，因为林德赫斯特是这么说的。
thing we want to use === everywhere because that's what Lyndhurst says.
实际上你所做的是向读者发送错误的语义信号
What you are actually doing is sending the wrong semantic signal to a reader of
你的代码。
your code.
我在所有这些情况下都是在保护自己，因为我不知道
Which is I’m protecting myself in all of these cases because I don't know about
类型。
the types.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这不是在传达你想要传达的东西
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And that is not communicating what you put to communicate
面向代码的未来读者。
to future readers of the code.
看到语义信号的代码的未来读者，
Future readers of the code that see the semantic signal,
我不知道类型，所以我不得不退回到一些=保护我自己，
I don't know about the types, so I've to fall back to some === to protect myself,
代码的那些未来的读取者更有可能重写代码，
those future readers of the code are much more likely to rewrite the code,
因为他们不明白。
because they don't understand it.
他们会做你第一次就该做的事
They're gonna do what you should have done the first time.
他们会把它重构到已知类型的地方。
They're gonna refactor it to where the types are known.
不确定性对您的代码基础不是一件好事。
Uncertainty is not a good thing for your code basis.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：总之，让你的类型为人所知
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So in summary, making your types known and
显然只会导致更好的代码。
obvious just leads to better code.
没有可以反驳的论点。
There's no argument that can be made to the contrary.
知道类型会导致更好的代码，如果类型是已知的，=总是最好的。
Knowing the types leads to better code and if the types are known, == is always best.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：在每种情况下，当类型已知且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: In every scenario == is best when the types are known and
在任何不能的情况下，您都应该回退到=。
in any scenario where you can't you should fall back to ===.
我很清楚这个案子很有争议。
I'm fully aware that case is quite controversial.
你们中的任何一个人目前都不太可能被这一点所说服
And it's unlikely that any of you are convinced at the moment by that
讨论。
discussion.
但我真正想问你的是回去考虑一下。
But what I would really like to ask you is to go back and think about it.
回去测试这个基本原理，并根据您的代码对其进行测试。
Go back and test this rationale and test it against your code.
问问你自己，你是否真的在写更好的更清晰的代码
Ask yourself if you really are writing better code that is more clearly
通过简单地使用=Everywhere来传达其意图。
communicating its intent by simply using === everywhere.
我不能为你做这些决定，但是
I can't make those decisions for you but
我想我已经尽我所能提出了最可靠的理由，为什么他们应该被重新分析。
I think I've made the most solid case that I can, for why they should be re-analysed.